{
   
   
    "q1":{
            "question" : "1. An example of a CSS shorthand property is ",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "Position",
                "option2" : "Font",
                "option3" : "Image",
                "option4" : "Display"
                },
            "answer" : "2"
            },
       
    "q2":{
            "question" : "2. What is the “hasLayout” property?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "It is the converse of the “hasNoLayout “ property",
                "option2" : "It is a property that can be set to either “left” or “right”",
                "option3" : "It is an internal property, which is IE-specific",
                "option4" : "It is a way to explicitly place an element in an HTML table"
                },
            "answer" : "3"
            }, 
    
    "q3":{
            "question" : "3. Which of the following is correct syntax when using the @media rule?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "@ media screen;print",
                "option2" : "@ media 'screen''print'",
                "option3" : "@ media screen print",
                "option4" : "@ media screen,print"
                },
            "answer" : "4"
            },
    
    "q4":{
            "question" : "4. What is your father NameFrom inside to out, the CSS Box Model includes ___________",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "Content, padding, border, and margin",
                "option2" : "Content, padding, and margin",
                "option3" : "Box, padding, and margin",
                "option4" : "Box, padding, border, and margin"
                },
            "answer" : "1"
            },
    
    "q5":{
            "question" : "5. Identify the valid declaration.",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "Border-style: dotted solid;",
                "option2" : "Border-style: dotted solid double dashed;",
                "option3" : "Border-style: dotted;",
                "option4" : "All of the above"
                },
            "answer" : "4"
            },
    
    "q6":{
            "question" : "6. Which of the following statements is NOT true regarding Style sheets?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "There is a limit as to how many external style sheets some browsers will read",
                "option2" : "Using multiple external style sheets is not advisable",
                "option3" : "Internal and external style sheets can be used in conjunction with each other",
                "option4" : "On any given web page, you can selectively link one or more external spreadsheets"
                },
            "answer" : "2"
            },
     "q7":{
            "question" : "7. The total width of a div styled as per the below CSS is _________ div { width: 100px; padding-right: 10px; margin: 10px; }",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "130px",
                "option2" : "120px",
                "option3" : "100px",
                "option4" : "110px"
                },
            "answer" : "1"
            },
       
    "q8":{
            "question" : "8. A global style sheet can be used to affect and style elements _____________",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "Only when the element has either an ID or a class",
                "option2" : "Only when the element has an ID",
                "option3" : "Only when the element has a class",
                "option4" : "Regardless of whether or not the element has an ID or a class"
                },
            "answer" : "4"
            }, 
    
    "q9":{
            "question" : "9. The CSS 'outline' property includes:",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "Style, color and width",
                "option2" : "Ordered vs. unordered setting",
                "option3" : "Indent level",
                "option4" : "Symbol vs. numeric setting"
                },
            "answer" : "1"
            },
    
    "q10":{
            "question" : "10. The 'font' shorthand property allows us to specify the following within a single declaration",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "Font style, weight, decoration, and family",
                "option2" : "Font family and size, but not line-height",
                "option3" : "Font style, weight, size, line-height, and family",
                "option4" : "Font family and size, but not style"
                },
            "answer" : "3"
            }
}
    
   
   
   
  